gospelinlife.com 2019-06-19

# Privacy Policy - Gospel in Life

## Who we are

We our resource site providing sermons, talks, studies, book recommendations, and more from Redeemer Churches and Ministries and Timothy Keller. Our website address is: https://gospelinlife.com.

## What personal data we collect and why we collect it

### E-Commerce Details

We collect information about you during the checkout process on our store. This information may include, but is not limited to, your name, billing address, shipping address, email address, phone number, credit card/payment details and any other details that might be requested from you for the purpose of processing your orders.  
Handling this data also allows us to:  
– Send you important account/order/service information.  
– Respond to your queries, refund requests, or complaints.  
– Process payments and to prevent fraudulent transactions. We do this on the basis of our legitimate business interests.  
– Set up and administer your account, provide technical and/or customer support, and to verify your identity.

Additionally we may also collect the following information:  
– Location and traffic data (including IP address and browser type) if you place an order, or if we need to estimate taxes and shipping costs based on your location.  
– Product pages visited and content viewed while your session is active.  
– Your comments and product reviews if you choose to leave them on our website.  
– Account email/password to allow you to access your account, if you have one.  
– If you choose to create an account with us, your name, address, and email address, which will be used to populate the checkout for future orders.

### Comments

When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.

### Cookies

If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.

### Embedded content from other websites

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. YouTube and Vimeo videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

### Analytics

## Who we share your data with

## How long we retain your data

If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.

For users that register on our website, we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.

## What rights you have over your data

If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

## Where we send your data

Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.

## Your contact information

You can contact us at anytime by emailing support@gospelinlife.com, calling 917-206-1422 or mailing a letter to the address below:

Gospel in Life  
1166 Avenue of the Americas, 16th Floor  
New York, NY 10036

## Additional information

### How we protect your data

Your profile data is stored on one of the industry leading hosting providers, WPEngine. We go an extra step beyond their great security practices and also partner with the security firm Sucuri to provide a 24/7 Firewall and Monitoring service. Your payment information is handled securely by Stripe and never touches our servers. We also partner with a development team to regular provide site maintenance and updates.

### What data breach procedures we have in place

In the very unlikely event of a data breach, we promise to contact you within 72 hours from the when it’s first discovered.
